Contact

sophiatoukram@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sophiatoukram (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Luxury Lifestyle Google Ads

Sophia Toukram

5 languages speaker looking for a great experience Casablanca Metropolitan Area

Summary

dream~establish~Work~motivate~focus~Success. /

Any kind of experience is always a great lesson to learn to move forward success. /

Multilingual, passionate, optimistic and communicative person who loves traveling & learning more about different cultures. /

Born leader.

Experience

Eden Roc Cap Cana 6 months

Sales and Reservation Agent August 2018 - October 2018 (3 months)

Dominican Republic

Taking reservations and selling for the Hotel services through phone calls and emails. Working with individuals, Travel Agencies and Tour Operators from all over the world.

Proceeding with prepayments, and elaborating invoices.

Fully operating Opera System.

Adminitrative Assistant Housekeeping Manager May 2018 - July 2018 (3 months) Dominican Republic

Ellaborating Reports.

Ordering and Recieving commodity.

Reaserch and innovating concepts.

Supervising the operation on field.

Participating in interviews.

Royal Mansour Marrakech
F&B and Kitchen Administrative Asistant

Page 1 of 2

August 2017 - October 2017 (3 months)

Marrakech Prefecture, Morocco

F&B and Kitchen Administrative Assistant

Working on new projects: Designing a new concept for in room breakfast and in Restaurant breakfast

Working on the opening of "the Royal Golf" and its concepts

Events coordinator assistant: making up proposals for different events (Food and Beverage options, locations, mood, decoration...) and helping in managing the organization of the event.

Taj Hotels Palaces Resorts Safaris F&B Internship July 2016 - October 2016 (4 months) Maldives

Waitress at the PoolSide Restaurant for lunch and Hostess for dinner at the fine dining restaurant DeepEnd.

Opening and Closing reports

Administrative Manager assistant

Mamounia F&B Internship March 2016 - April 2016 (2 months) Marrakech

Selman Marrakech Front and Back Office departments Internship December 2015 - January 2016 (2 months) Marrakech

Reception and Reservations
General Housekeeper Assistant

Education

HTL International School of Hospitality, Tourism and Languages Master's degree, Luxury and Vip management in tourism · (2019 - 2019)

UIC

Bachelor's degree, Hospitality Administration/Management · (2015 - 2018)